[A] yep : shes flashing at least three hundred grand on her carcass
[B] and now our own song stylist and everybody baby .. jeri erome cmon j get off those hands , folks !
[A] hi ya , marie so ya sneaked out after all c ' mon in an well dance !
[B] gosh noi don ' t want any one to see me ! they might tell mrs . kingsbury
[A] halt who goes there ?
[B] only me -- elmer ! i would like to know i go about becoming a mouse , please p
[A] sama its that guy o ' connor we saw his picture in the sheriff ' s office !
[B] well , what do you know keep him covered , mike ill go back for the sheriff !
[A] are indians really as wild as they were in the movie unk ?
[B] no but they used to be
[A] sheena escape stop her !
[B] f you have been brave now go rest ! i shall takeover the watch ?